#### Contact

rcastaneto22@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/rommelcastaneto-msn-rn-7548b9a2 (LinkedIn)

#### Top Skills

**ACLS** 

Inpatient

Medical-Surgical

#### Languages

Tagalog

# Rommel Castaneto, MSN, RN

Nurse Manager at Mount Sinai West

New York, New York

## Summary

Experienced Nursing Manager with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Strong healthcare services professional skilled in Psychiatric Nursing, Substance Abuse, Methadone Treatment, Nursing Education, Patient Safety, and Healthcare Information Technology (HIT)

## Experience

Mount Sinai West Nurse Manager August 2019 - Present (1 year)

Nurse Manager for the Behavioral Health Department, CPEP, Addiction Institute, and OTP Methadone Program

Mount Sinai St. Luke's and Mount Sinai West Registered Nurse June 2016 - Present (4 years 2 months) Greater New York City Area

White Glove Placement, Inc Registered Nurse January 2014 - August 2019 (5 years 8 months)

Emerald Medical Management RN August 2011 - December 2013 (2 years 5 months)

Huntington Beach Hospital
Charge Nurse
June 2011 - December 2013 (2 years 7 months)

## Education

#### Western Governors University

Master's degree, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2014 - 2016)

#### West Coast University

Associate of Arts and Sciences (A.A.S.), Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse  $\cdot$  (2009 - 2011)